<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>exercises on Quantum Computing</title><link>https://tonnidas.github.io/quantum-exercises/categories/exercises/</link><description>Recent content in exercises on Quantum Computing</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2021, Tonni Das Jui; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tonnidas.github.io/quantum-exercises/categories/exercises/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Documents</title><link>https://tonnidas.github.io/quantum-exercises/post/docs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonnidas.github.io/quantum-exercises/post/docs/</guid><description>Instructor&amp;rsquo;s Lecture Documents Lecture Slides 01 Basic concepts on Quantum Computing 02 Classical Concepts 03 Quantum Concepts 04 Basic Quantum Definitions 05 Newtonian Mechanics 06 Branches of Physics 07 Introduction to Quantum Computing 08 Universality 09 Quantum Gates 10 QFT 11 Oracle Colab Repositories 01 Introduction 02 Bernstein-Vazirani Algorithm 03 Quantum Phase Estimation Notes 01 note1 01 note2</description></item><item><title>Mini Project</title><link>https://tonnidas.github.io/quantum-exercises/post/mini-project/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonnidas.github.io/quantum-exercises/post/mini-project/</guid><description>When: In summer2 of 2021, I took the Quantum-Computing course provided by baylor. Why: I did the mini-project as it was a part of the course. Every student was required to complete a quantum mini-project and I chose to work with classifiers. Abstract: In recent years, researchers are looking into data transformations in the quantum information space to see whether they may improve robustness and performance.</description></item><item><title>Final Exercises Solutions</title><link>https://tonnidas.github.io/quantum-exercises/post/ex1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tonnidas.github.io/quantum-exercises/post/ex1/</guid><description>As the final assignment of Quantum-Computing course, I solved the following problems. Here, is the ten Problems and solutions to the five problems out of ten of the final assignment.
Problems
Solutions</description></item></channel></rss>